[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these dinosaurs was herbivorous?", "correct_answer": "Protoceratops", "incorrect_answers": ["Velociraptor", "Tyrannosaurus", "Allosaurus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In contract bridge, Jacoby transfers are a convention used by a responder following what kind of opening bid?", "correct_answer": "Trump opening bid", "incorrect_answers": ["3 spades", "2 clubs", "Any opening bid"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In trigonometry, the tangent is defined as what?", "correct_answer": "The sine divided by the cosine", "incorrect_answers": ["The ratio of the side adjacent to the angle to the side opposite the angle", "The reciprocal of the cosine", "The negative logarithm of the cotangent"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "People who suffer from this condition tend to be self-destructive. They may use drugs, or engage in promiscuous sexual activities.", "correct_answer": "Borderline Personality Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Obsessive Compulsive Disorder", "Panic Disorder", "Generalized Anxiety Disorder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used for the preparation of the popular Arab meal called Shish taouk?", "correct_answer": "Chicken", "incorrect_answers": ["Beef", "Lamb", "Duck"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the three suits of Mahjong?", "correct_answer": "stones, bamboos, characters", "incorrect_answers": ["bamboos, winds, characters", "dragons, winds, characters", "dragons, stones, bamboos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Disney movie Princess Protection Program, Rosies first job was in a smoothie shop.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Despite sharks\u2019 bad reputation thanks to movies out of 300 species of sharks only this much are known to have attacked and killed a man.", "correct_answer": "4", "incorrect_answers": ["10", "2", "11"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Movie Superman Returns, how does Lex Luthor plan to defeat Superman and kill billions of people?", "correct_answer": "by using one of the stolen Kryptonian crystals", "incorrect_answers": ["none of these", "by shooting a Kryponite bullet at Superman", "by blowing up the world"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does RAM stand for?", "correct_answer": "Random Access Memory", "incorrect_answers": ["ReadAble Memory", "Raise All Memory", "Erase All Memory"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are cheetahs that have mutated patterning that creates blotches instead of spots called?", "correct_answer": "King Cheetahs", "incorrect_answers": ["Smudge Cheetahs", "Black Cheetahs", "Striped Cheetahs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which actor made the following remark: Wheres my manners? Its 11 oclock; you must be parched.?", "correct_answer": "Tom Hanks in The Money Pit", "incorrect_answers": ["Jean Smart in Protocol", "Robin Williams in Good Morning, Vietnam", "Bette Midler in Down and Out in Beverly Hills"]}]